Mercury Press Records
Mercury Press Records
- Fantasy and Science Fiction (Part II)
  - Editorial records
    - Literary manuscripts
      - Moore, Ward
        - "Measure of a Man", Aug 1953 (Box 77)
        - "No Man Pursueth", Apr 1956 (Box 77)
      - Morrison, William
        - "The Inner Worlds", Apr 1954 (Box 77)
      - Morrissey, Doug
        - "The Mind in the Manila Folder", undated (Box 77)
      - Moskowitz, Sam
        - "The Genealogy of the Term 'Science Fiction'", 26 Jul 1956 (Box 77)
        - "The Strange Business of the Science Fiction Industry", circa Jul 1955 (Box 77)
      - Mudgett, Herman W.
        - "The Glass of the Future", undated (Box 77)
        - "Report on the Sexual Behavior of the Extra-Sensory Perceptor", Aug 1954 (Box 77)
      - Murphy, Maurice
        - "Time Tourist", Feb 1951 (Box 77)
      - Murphy, Phyllis
        - "Time Was", Oct 1968 (Box 77)
      - Nathan, Robert
        - "Encounter in the Past", Jul 1967 (Box 77)
      - Nearing, H., Jr.
        - "The Actinic Actor", Apr 1952 (Box 77)
        - "The Cerebrative Psittacoid", Aug 1953 (Box 77)
        - "The Embarrassing Dimension", Aug 1951 (Box 77)
        - "The Factitious Pentangle", Sep 1952 (Box 77)
        - "The Gastronomical Error", Dec 1953 (Box 77)
        - "The Hyperspherical Basketball", Dec 1951 (Box 77)
        - "The Maladjusted Classroom", Jun 1953 (Box 77)
        - "The Malignant Organ", Mar 1953 (Box 77)
        - "The Mathematical Voodoo", Apr (?) 1951 (Box 77)
        - "The Unidentified Amazon", Dec 1952 (Box 77)
      - Nelson, Alan
        - "Cattivo", Aug 1951 (Box 77)
        - "The Gualcophone", Aug 1952 (Box 77)
        - "The Shopdropper", Jan 1955 (Box 77)
        - "Silenzia", Sep 1953 (Box 77)
        - "Soap Opera", Apr 1953 (Box 77)
      - Neville, Kris
        - "It Pays to Advertise", Jun 1953 (Box 77)
        - "Mission", Apr 1953 (Box 77)
        - "Old Man Henderson", Jun 1951 (Box 77)
        - "Underground Movement", undated (Box 77)
      - Niven, Larry
        - "Dry Run", May 1968 (Box 77)
        - "The Long Night", Mar 1967 (Box 77)
        - "The Meddler", Oct 1968 (Box 77)
        - "Not Long Before the End", Apr 1969 (Box 77)
        - "Safe at Speed", May 1967 (Box 77)
      - Nolan, William F.
        - "Charles Beaumont: 'The Magic Man'", Jun 1967 (Box 77)
        - "He Kilt it With a Stick", Feb 1968 (Box 77)
      - Norbert, W.
        - "The Miracle of the Broom Closet", Feb 1954 (Box 77)
      - Norton, Andre
        - "Mousetrap", Jun 1954 (Box 77)
      - Novotny, John
        - "The Bourbon Lake", Dec 1954 (Box 77)
        - "On Camera", Apr 1956 (Box 77)
      - O'Brien, Fitz-James
        - "The Lost Room", 1949, Fall (Box 78)
        - "The Wondersmith", Dec 1950 (Box 78)
      - O'Donnell, K. M.
        - "Death to the Keeper", Aug 1968 (Box 78)
        - "Final War", Apr 1968 (Box 78)
        - "How I Take Their Measure", Jan 1969 (Box 78)
      - Oliver, Chad
        - "The Boy Next Door", Jun 1951 (Box 78)
        - "Shadows in the Sun", 17 Jul 1953 (Box 78)
        - "Transformer", Nov 1954 (Box 78)
      - Onions, Olivet
        - "Rooum", 1949, Fall (Box 78)
      - Oppenheim, Garrett
        - "The Punishing of Eddie Jungle Spit", Aug 1951 (Box 78)
      - Ottum, Bob
        - "Chirp Me a Story", Aug 1955 (Box 78)
      - Palmer, Stuart
        - "A Bride for the Devil", 1949, Fall (Box 78)
      - Palmer, Stuart & Jennifer
        - "Brainwave", Dec 1967 (Box 78)
      - Parker, Richard
        - "The Wheelbarrow Boy", Mar 1953 (Box 78)
      - Paul, Herb
        - "The Angel With Purple Hair", Dec 1950 (Box 78)
      - Pearson, Martin & Corwin, Cecil
        - "The Mask of Demeter", Jan 1953 (Box 78)
      - Pederson, Con
        - "The August People", Jun 1953 (Box 78)
      - Petaja, Emil
        - "Where is Thy Sting?", May 1967 (Box 78)
      - Peterson, Phyllis Lee
        - "Pamela Pays the Piper", 1950, Fall (Box 78)
      - Phelan, Jeremiah
        - "The Episode of the Perilous Talisman", Feb 1951 (Box 78)
      - Phillips, Peter
        - "C/O Mr. Makepeace", Feb 1954 (Box 78)
        - "The Warning", Sep 1953 (Box 78)
      - Porges, Arthur
        - "By a Fluke", Oct 1955 (Box 78)
        - "The Devil and Simon Flagg", Aug 1954 (Box 78)
        - "The Fly", Sep 1952 (Box 78)
        - "The Grom", Nov 1954 (Box 78)
        - "The Liberator", Dec 1953 (Box 78)
        - "The Logic of Rufus Weir", Nov 1955 (Box 78)
        - "Mop Up", Jul 1953 (Box 78)
        - "One Dollar and Ninety-Eight Cents", May 1954 (Box 78)
        - "The Ruum", Oct 1953 (Box 78)
        - "Story Conference", May 1953 (Box 78)
        - "Strange Birth", Jun 1953 (Box 78)
        - "The Tidings", Feb 1955 (Box 78)
      - Priestley, J. B.
        - "Night Sequence", Mar 1956 (Box 78)
        - "The Strange Girl", Jan 1954 (Box 78)
        - "Uncle Phil on TV", Oct 1955 (Box 78)
      - Purdom, Thomas E.
        - "There is a Reason for Space Travel", Oct 1955 (Box 78)
      - Purdom, Tom
        - "Reduction in Arms", Aug 1967 (Box 78)
      - Quattrocchi, Franic
        - "He Had a Big Heart", Mar 1955 (Box 78)
      - Raimondo, Dennis
        - "In Search of Comment", May 1968 (Box 78)
      - Randolph, Vance
        - "Blood in the Cellar: An Ozark Folk Tale", undated (Box 78)
        - "Slipping Through the Keyhole", Feb 1953 (Box 78)
        - "The Yellow Catfish", Nov 1952 (Box 78)
      - Ready, W. B.
        - "Devlin", Apr 1953 (Box 78)
        - "The Giant Finn MacCool", Feb 1952 (Box 78)
        - "The Hound of Cullen", Nov 1953 (Box 78)
        - "Weerawannas", Jun 1953 (Box 78)
      - Ready, William
        - "The Short story", 14 Feb 1952 (Box 78)
      - Redd, David
        - "A Quiet Kind of Madness", May 1968 (Box 78)
        - "Sundown", Dec 1967 (Box 78)
      - Redman, Ben Ray
        - "At the Door", Aug 1953 (Box 78)
      - Reed, Kit
        - "The Vine", Nov 1967 (Box 78)
      - Reines, Donald F.
        - "The Shape of Copyright to Come", Apr 1953 (Box 78)
      - Reynolds, L. Major
        - "Flood", Feb 1952 (Box 78)
      - Reynolds, Mack
        - "And Thou Beside Me", Apr 1954 (Box 79)
        - "The Business as Usual", undated (Box 79)
        - "The Expert", Jan 1955 (Box 79)
        - "The Other Alternative", Feb 1954 (Box 79)
        - "Prone", Sep 1954 (Box 79)
        - "Relic", Mar 1967 (Box 79)
      - Reynolds, Mack & Derleth, August
        - "The Adventure of the Snitch in Time", Jul 1953 (Box 79)
      - Rhodes, W. H.
        - "The Case of Summerfield", 1950, Summer (Box 79)
      - Richardson, Robert S.
        - "The Day After We Land on Mars!", Dec 1955 (Box 79)
      - Rieth, Lee
        - "The Long Walk", 22 Aug 1957 (Box 79)
      - Rigsby, Howard
        - "One Fine Day", Sep 1954 (Box 79)
      - Roberts, Jane
        - "The String of Beads", undated (Box 79)
      - Robin, Ralph
        - "The Beach Thing", undated (Box 79)
        - "Budding Explorer", Sep 1952 (Box 79)
        - "Inefficiency Expert", Mar 1953 (Box 79)
        - "Mr. Prime", Jun 1953 (Box 79)
        - "Open Ears", Aug 1953 (Box 79)
      - Rogers, Joel Townsley
        - "Beyond Space and Time", undated (Box 79)
      - Rogers, Kay
        - "The Bitterness of Ghoril", Apr 1952 (Box 79)
        - "Command Performance", Aug 1954 (Box 79)
        - "Experiment", Feb 1953 (Box 79)
        - "Letter to a Tiger", Oct 1953 (Box 79)
        - "Love Story", Jun 1951 (Box 79)
      - Rosny Aine, J. H.
        - "The Shapes", Mar 1968 (Box 79)
      - Royce, Stewart
        - "...Flight in the Hills", Nov 1953 (Box 79)
      - Russ, Joanna
        - "A Short and Happy Life", Jun 1969 (Box 79)
      - Saari, Oliver
        - "The Space Man", Apr 1953 (Box 79)
      - Saberhagen, Fred
        - "Young Girl at an Open Half-Door", Nov 1968 (Box 79)
      - St. Clair, Eric
        - "The Motorman's Glove", Apr 1956 (Box 79)
        - "Too Many Bears", Sep 1955 (Box 79)
      - Saki
        - "The Hedgehog", Dec 1955 (Box 79)
        - "The Music on the Hill", Sep 1955 (Box 79)
        - "The Seventh Pullet", Dec 1954 (Box 79)
        - "The Wolves at Cernogratz", Mar 1956 (Box 79)
      - Sale, Richard
        - "The Old Oaken Eight-Ball", Sep 1953 (Box 79)
        - "Perseus Had a Helmet", 1949, Fall (Box 79)
      - Sambrot, William
        - "Night of the Leopard", Sep 1967 (Box 79)
      - Sansom, William
        - "The Tournament", Jan 1955 (Box 79)
      - Saxton, Josephine
        - "The Consciousness Machine", Jun 1968 (Box 79)
        - "Dormant Soul", Feb 1969 (Box 79)
        - "Light on Cader", Jan 1968 (Box 79)
        - "Nothing Much to Relate", Nov 1967 (Box 79)
      - Schenck, Hilbert, Jr.
        - "Tomorrow's Weather", Apr 1953 (Box 79)
      - Schenk, L. F.
        - "Full Value Received", 21 Dec 1957 (Box 79)
      - Schmitz, James H.
        - "Attitudes", Feb 1968 (Box 79)
      - Schneider, Raymond
        - "The Micromen", circa Jul 1956 (Box 79)
      - Schoenfeld, Howard
        - "Built Down Logically", Dec 1951 (Box 79)
        - "Built Up Logically", 1950, Fall (Box 79)
        - "Hasty Conclusion", circa Oct 1949 (Box 79)
      - Schutz, J. W.
        - "The Bubble", Aug 1967 (Box 79)
        - "The Star Driver", Jan 1967 (Box 79)
      - Seabright, Idris
        - "Asking", Nov 1955 (Box 80)
        - "Brightness Falls From the Air", Apr (?) 1951 (Box 80)
        - "The Causes", undated (Box 80)
        - "An Egg a Month From All Over", undated (Box 80)
        - "The Hole in the Moon", Feb 1952 (Box 80)
        - "The Listening Child", Dec 1950 (Box 80)
        - "The Man Who Sold Rope to the Gnoles", Oct 1951 (Box 80)
        - "The New Ritual", Jan 1953 (Box 80)
      - Searles, Baird
        - "The Wilis", May 1968 (Box 80)
      - Seeley, Mabel
        - "The Foot Print", Jan 1953 (Box 80)
      - Sellings, Arthur
        - "Crack in the Shield", Jan 1968 (Box 80)
        - "The Legend and the Chemistry", Jan 1969 (Box 80)
      - Shaara, Michael
        - "Grenville's Planet", Oct 1952 (Box 80)
        - "Time Payment", Jun 1954 (Box 80)
      - Sheckley, Robert
        - "Budget Planet", Mar 1968 (Box 80)
        - "The King's Wishes", Jul 1953 (Box 80)
        - "The Monsters", Mar 1953 (Box 80)
        - "The People Trap", Jun 1968 (Box 80)
      - Sheckley, Robert & Ellison, Harlan
        - "I See a Man Sitting on a Chair, and the Chair is Biting His Leg", Jan 1968 (Box 80)
      - Sheldon, Walt
        - "A Rope For Lucifer", 1950, Winter - Spring (Box 80)
      - Siegel, Larry
        - "Another Chance For Casey", Dec 1950 (Box 80)
        - "Dead-Eye Daniel", Nov 1954 (Box 80)
      - Silverberg, Robert
        - "The Fangs of the Trees", Oct 1968 (Box 80)
        - "Sundance", Jun 1969 (Box 80)
      - Sladek, John
        - "A Report on the Migrations of Educational Materials", Dec 1968 (Box 80)
      - Slesar, Henry
        - "The Moving Finger Types", Sep 1968 (Box 80)
      - Smith, Evelyn E.
        - "Calliope and Gherkin and the Yankee Doodle Thing", Mar 1969 (Box 80)
        - "Gerda", Apr 1954 (Box 80)
        - "The Last of the Spode", Jun 1953 (Box 80)
        - "The Martian and the Magician", Nov 1952 (Box 80)
      - Spivak, Lawrence
        - "Introduction", 1949, Fall (Box 80)
      - Springer, Sherwood
        - "Epitaph Near Moonport", Jan 1954 (Box 80)
        - "Epitaph on Rigel XII" & Epitaph in Avalon", Jul 1954 (Box 80)
      - Stanton, Will
        - "Barney", Feb 1951 (Box 80)
        - "The Girl in the Flaxen Convertible", Oct 1954 (Box 80)
        - "The Pioneer", May 1954 (Box 80)
      - Sterling, J. D.
        - "The Hand and the Jug of Mead", Mar 1954 (Box 80)
      - Stevenson, Robert Louis
        - "The Isle of Voices", Jan 1953 (Box 80)
        - "The Song of the Meadow", Feb 1967 (Box 80)
      - Struther, Jan
        - "Ugly Sister", Feb 1952 (Box 80)
      - Sturgeon, Theodore
        - "The Hurkle is a Happy Beast", 1949, Fall (Box 80)
        - "The Silken-Swift", Nov 1953 (Box 80)
      - Sullivan, Edward S.
        - "The 8:29", Feb 1952 (Box 80)
      - Summers, S. E.
        - "Dyne-oplane or Flying Saucer?", circa Mar 1953 (Box 80)
      - Tale, Peter
        - "The Day the Wind Died", Mar 1969 (Box 80)
      - Taylor, Graves
        - "The Roommate", Feb 1951 (Box 80)
      - Taylor, Robert
        - "A Sense of Beauty", Aug 1968 (Box 80)
      - Thomas, Gilbert
        - "...But For the Grace of God", Jun 1967 (Box 80)
        - "Butterfly Was Is", Sep 1968 (Box 80)
      - Thomas, Ted
        - "The Science Springboard", 1967, Jan, Feb, Apr, May, Aug; 1968, Feb (Box 80)
      - Trott, Susan
        - "Donny Baby", Sep 1967 (Box 80)
      - Tucker, Wilson
        - "Able to Zebra", Mar 1953 (Box 80)
        - "To a Ripe Old Age", Dec 1952 (Box 80)
      - Tushnet, Leonard
        - "The Chelmlins", Dec 1967 (Box 81)
        - "Gifts From the Universe", May 1968 (Box 81)
        - "The Worm Shamir", Dec 1968 (Box 81)
      - United States Air Force
        - "Unidentified Aerial Objects", Apr 1956 (Box 81)
      - Van Dyck, Robert S.
        - "Conception", undated (Box 81)
      - Van Scyoc, Sydney
        - "Unidentified Fallen Object", Jan 1969 (Box 81)
      - Van Vogt, A. E.
        - "Process", Dec 1950 (Box 81)
      - Wainwright, Ruth Laura
        - "Mint, in D/J", Jun 1954 (Box 81)
      - Wakefield, H. R.
        - "Professor Pownall's Oversight", 1950, Summer (Box 81)
        - "The Gorge of the Churels", Oct 1951 (Box 81)
      - Wanley, Nathaniel
        - "The Wonders of the Little World", Feb 1952 (Box 81)
      - Webb, Charles T.
        - "Bem", Nov 1952 (Box 81)
      - Wellman, Manly Wade
        - "Call Me From the Valley", Mar 1954 (Box 81)
        - "The Desrick on Yandro", undated (Box 81)
        - "Dumb Supper", 12 Aug 1953 (Box 81)
        - "Larroes Catch Meddlers", Apr (?) 1951 (Box 81)
        - "O Ugly Bird", Dec 1951 (Box 81)
        - "On the Hills and Everywhere", Jan 1956 (Box 81)
        - "One Other", Aug 1953 (Box 81)
        - "Vandy, Vandy", Mar 1953 (Box 81)
      - Wendel, Hilda
        - "Cyprian's Room", May 1967 (Box 81)
      - White, Ted
        - "Wednesday, Noon", Feb 1968 (Box 81)
      - White, William Chapman
        - "The Literate Monster", Apr (?) 1956 (Box 81)
      - Wilde, Percival
        - "The Extreme Airiness of Duton Lang", undated (Box 81)
      - Wilder, William M.
        - "Request, Desperate", 22 May 1958 (Box 81)
      - Wilhelm, Kate
        - "Stranger in the House", Feb 1968 (Box 81)
      - Williams, Lita
        - "Flight Into Madness", circa Aug 1955 (Box 81)
        - "The Receptive Ones", circa Aug 1955 (Box 81)
      - Williams, Robert Moore
        - "Aurochs Came Walking", Dec 1953 (Box 81)
      - Wilson, Gahan
        - "Harry's Golden Years", Sep 1968 (Box 81)
        - "The Knight-Errant, the Dragon and the Maiden", Jan 1967 (Box 81)
        - "The Power of the Mandirin", Dec 1967 (Box 81)
        - "The Sea Monster and the Mayor of New York City", Jul 1967 (Box 81)
      - Wilson, Richard
        - "Love", undated (Box 81)
      - Winslow, Thyra Samter
        - "Rudolph", Sep 1955 (Box 81)
      - Wodhams, Jack
        - "A Run of Deuces", undated (Box 81)
      - Wolf, Leonard
        - "Some Facts About Robots", Jul 1954 (Box 81)
      - Wood, Christopher
        - "The Enemy", Feb 1953 (Box 81)
        - "Miss Frost", Apr? 1951 (Box 81)
        - "Mrs. Dalrymple's Cat", Sep 1953 (Box 81)
      - Wyndham, John
        - "Bargain From Brunswick", Jun 1951 (Box 81)
        - "Jizzle", Feb 1952 (Box 81)
        - "The Perfect Creature", Jan 1953 (Box 81)
      - Yefremov, I.
        - "A Secret From Hellas", Sep 1967 (Box 81)
      - Young, Robert F.
        - "Kingdom Come, Inc.", Jan 1967 (Box 81)
      - Zelazny, Roger
        - "Dawn", Apr 1967 (Box 81)
        - "Death and the Executioner", Jun 1967 (Box 81)
    - Receipt of manuscripts file, undated (Box 82)
    - Reprint acceptances
      - Dickens, Charles
        - "The Rat That Could Speak", Aug 1951 (Box 82)
      - Greene, Graham
        - "A Discovery in the Woods", Jun 1967 (Box 82)
      - Harrison, Michael
        - "The Heart of It", Jun 1968 (Box 82)
      - Huneker, James G.
        - "The Disenchanted Symphony", Jan 1967 (Box 82)
      - Manhattan, Avro
        - "The Cricket Ball", Oct 1955 (Box 82)
      - Merrill, Judith
        - "Once and Future Tales From the Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction" introduction, 1968 (Box 82)
      - Poe, Edgar Allen
        - "Mellonta Tauta", Dec 1955 (Box 82)
      - Tarkington, Booth
        - "The Veiled Feminists of Atlantis", Feb 1968 (Box 82)
      - Thurber, James
        - "II: If Grant Had Been Drinking at Appomattox", Feb 1952 (Box 82)
      - Vandercook, John W.
        - "The Challenge", Mar 1956 (Box 82)
      - Varshaysky, Ilya
        - "The Conflict", Aug 1967 (Box 82)
      - Watt, T. S.
        - "Visitors From Venus", Jun 1954 (Box 82)
      - Whitley, George
        - "Second Meeting", 1950, Fall (Box 82)
      - Wodehouse, P. G.
        - "Mulliner's Buck-U-Uppo", Dec 1955 (Box 82)
        - "Unpleasantness at Bludleigh Court", Oct 1952 (Box 82)
      - Zamyatin, Yevgeny
        - "The Cave", Feb 1969 (Box 82)
    - Reprint fragments, undated (Box 82)
    - Reprint submissions
      - A - R, 7 folders (Box 82)
      - S - Z, 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Style sheets, undated (Box 83)
    - Title pages, destroyed manuscripts (?), undated (Box 83)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 83)
    - Miscellaneous printed material, undated (Box 83)
  - Financial records
    - Check orders, 1949-1958; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Instructions for estimating cost, undated (Box 83)
    - Inventories, 1950-1958 (Box 83)
    - Manuscript costs, 1953-1955 (Box 83)
    - Royalty reports, 1950-1959; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948-1958 (Box 83)
  - Memorabilia
    - Brochures, badges, etc., undated (Box 83)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 83)
  - Production records
    - Bookdealer's advertising, undated (Box 84)
    - Cartoons
      - Ley, Olga, undated (Box 84)
      - Volinsky, Frank, undated (Box 84)
      - Wilson, Gahan, Dec 1968 (Box 84)
    - Covers, 1950-1958; 1967-1969,; undated; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Fillers, accepted, undated (Box 84)
    - Fillers, rejected, undated (Box 84)
    - Form letters, undated (Box 84)
    - French edition, undated (Box 84)
    - Galley and page proofs
      - Fragments, unidentified authors, 2 folders (Box 84)
      - Fragments A - K, 8 folders (Box 84)
      - Fragments L - Z, 6 folders (Box 85)
      - Index, Vol. 5, 1953, Jul-Dec (Box 85)
      - Abernathy, Robert
        - "Single Combat" (Box 85)
        - "The Year 2000" (Box 85)
      - Alden, W. L.
        - "Van Wagener's Ways" (Box 85)
      - Anderson, Poul
        - "Inside Straight" (Box 85)
        - "Operation Afreet" (Box 85)
        - "Three Hearts and Three Lions" (Box 85)
      - Anderson, Poul and Dickson, Gordon R.
        - "Joy in Mudville" (Box 85)
      - Asimov, Isaac
        - "I Just Make Them Up, Sees" (Box 85)
        - "The Message" (Box 85)
      - Beaumont, Charles
        - "The Science Screen" (Box 85)
      - Blish, James
        - "In Memoriam: Fletcher Pratt" (Box 85)
        - "With Malice to Come" (Box 85)
      - Bloch, Robert
        - "The Traveling Salesman" (Box 85)
      - Boucher, Anthony
        - "The Best From Fantasy and Science Fiction" Fourth Series (Box 85)
        - "The First" (Box 85)
        - "Recommended Reading" (Box 85)
      - Boucher, Anthony and McComas J. Francis
        - "The Best From Fantasy and Science Fiction, Third Series (Box 85)
        - "Recommended Reading" (Box 85)
        - "Verdict of Two" (Box 85)
      - Bradbury, Ray
        - "The Dragon" (Box 85)
        - "The Pedestrian" (Box 85)
      - Brode, Anthony
        - "Flying Chaucer" (Box 85)
        - "The Fourteenth of July" (Box 85)
        - "Mrs. Coward Gets There First" (Box 85)
      - Brookbank, Richard
        - "The Invisible Wall" (Box 85)
      - Broughton, Rhoda
        - "The Man With the Nose" (Box 85)
      - Buck, Doris P.
        - "Aunt Agatha" (Box 85)
        - "Curved Universe" (Box 85)
      - Chandler, A. Bertram
        - "Haunt" (Box 86)
      - Charteris, Leslie
        - "The Darker Drink" (Box 86)
      - Christie, Agatha
        - "The Fourth Man" (Box 86)
      - Clarke, Arthur
        - "Of Mind and Matter" (Box 86)
      - Clarke, Pauline
        - "The Potato Cake" (Box 86)
      - Clingerman, Mildred
        - "Minister Without Portfolio" (Box 86)
      - Coates, Robert M.
        - "The Return of the Gods" (Box 86)
      - Crow, Levi
        - "Warrior in Darkness" (Box 86)
      - Croy, Homer
        - "Cherokee Bill" (Box 86)
      - Davidson, Avram
        - "I Do Not Hear You, Sir" (Box 86)
      - Deardorf, Kenneth R.
        - "Ganymedeus Sapiens: Modern Scientific Dilemma" (Box 86)
      - deCamp, L. Sprague
        - "How to Talk Futurian" (Box 86)
        - "Lament" (Box 86)
      - deCamp, L. Sprague and Pratt, Fletcher
        - "The Ancestral Amethyst" (Box 86)
        - "The Blackball" (Box 86)
        - "Weissenbroch Spectacles" (Box 86)
      - deFord, Miriam Allen
        - "Frustrated Frankenstein: Alfonso Herrera and His Colpoids" (Box 86)
        - "The Last Generation?" (Box 86)
        - "Old Man Morgan's Grave" (Box 86)
      - Dickinson, Patric
        - "The Ape at the Typewriter" (Box 86)
      - Dickson, Gordon R.
        - "James" (Box 86)
      - Drake, Leah Bodine
        - "The Gods of the Dana" (Box 86)
      - Dunsany, Lord
        - "Misadventure" (Box 86)
      - Edmondson, G. C.
        - "Rescue" (Box 86)
      - Ellis, H. F.
        - "Space-Crime Continuum" (Box 86)
      - Farmer, Philip Jose
        - "Father" (Box 86)
        - "The Night of Light" (Box 86)
      - Finney, Charles
        - "The Black Retriever" (Box 86)
      - Finney, Jack
        - "The Third Level" (Box 86)
      - Friborg, Albert Compton
        - "Careless Love" (Box 86)
      - Fyfe, H. B.
        - "Ransom" (Box 86)
      - Garrett, Randall
        - "I've Got a Little List" (Box 86)
      - Grinnell, David
        - "The Rag Thing" (Box 86)
        - "Top Secret" (Box 86)
      - Heinlein, Robert A.
        - "Lummox" (Box 86)
      - Henderson, Zenna
        - "Ararat" (Box 86)
        - "Turn the Page" (Box 86)
      - Henexson, Glen
        - "Wish for the Moon" (Box 86)
      - Hope, Anthony
        - "My Astral Body" (Box 86)
      - Hubbard, P. M.
        - "Free Flight" (Box 86)
        - "Lion" (Box 86)
      - Humphreys, Emyr
        - "The Girl in the Ice" (Box 86)
      - Jones, Alice Eleanor
        - "Created He Them" (Box 86)
      - Kersh, Gerald
        - "The Terribly Wild Flowers" (Box 86)
      - Kneale, Nigel
        - "Peg" (Box 86)
      - Knight, Damon
        - "Eripmav" (Box 86)
      - McClintic, Winona
        - "The Anti-Climax" (Box 86)
        - "Bright Destruction" (Box 86)
        - "Valse Macabre" (Box 86)
        - "Ye Phantasie Writer and His Catte" (Box 86)
      - McComas, J. Francis
        - "Parallel" (Box 86)
      - M'Intosh (McIntosh), J. T.
        - "One Too Many" (Box 86)
        - "Selection" (Box 86)
        - "Talents" (Box 86)
      - Marsh, Willard
        - "Machina Ex Machina" (Box 86)
      - Matheson, Richard
        - "Pattern For Survival" (Box 86)
        - "The Test" (Box 86)
      - Moore, Ward
        - "Bring the Jubilee" (Box 86)
        - "Lot's Daughter" (Box 86)
      - Morrison, William
        - "The Ardent Soul" (Box 86)
        - "Music of the Sphere" (Box 86)
        - "The Science Stage" (Box 86)
      - Morton, J. B.
        - "On the Way to Her Sister" (Box 86)
      - Nash, Golden
        - "A Tale of the Thirteenth Floor" (Box 86)
      - Nelson, Alan
        - "The Shopdropper" (Box 86)
      - Nelson, Starr